Okay, are you ready?
There's nothing in here.
Hey, wait!
I'll be okay.
I'm not going in too far.
Besides, we should find out what
kind of boss we're dealing with.
How else are we gonna
figure out how to beat it?
Yeah, I know.
It's just...
I'm not sure what it is.
I've recognized that a terrible past,
I can't understand the
fact that I'm afraid.
I'm afraid of my back-to-face,
but I'm still in the future.
Thank you.
Oh, my!
I'm going to spread out.
I'm going to feel the weak of you,
I'm going to feel the weak of you!
I'm going to be strong in the world.
I want to always be waiting.
I'm giving everything I have.
That one's gonna be tough
to beat. You're right.
I saw you only had that one big sword, and
I'm pretty sure it's got special attacks,
too.
We're gonna have to put
tanks in the front row
and keep switching out
just to wear it down.
Yeah, and it wouldn't hurt to
have about ten shield users.
Shield users, huh?
What? What's wrong? You are.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
I just realized something.
The biggest advantage of using a one-handed
sword is you can also use a shield.
But you know what?
I don't think I've ever
seen you using one.
I don't use a shield because
it'll slow down my rapier.
Others don't because
they think it looks dumb.
And how come you're not using the
sword you commissioned from Liz?
Very suspicious.
Oh, never mind.
It's rude to ask people
to justify their skills.
Since it's gotten so late,
might as well have lunch here.
Really?
Did you make it yourself?
Yep.
But you better take your
gloves off before you eat.
Oh, sure.
Here you go.
This is good.
How'd you get it to taste so amazing?
Chalk it up to a whole
year of training and study.
Aincrad has everything you need.
There's about a hundred
different seasonings.
I made everything just
by calculating all the
parameters used by the
flavor recreation engine.
This was made with grokwa seed,
sugar leaf, and calum water.
It's mayonnaise.
And I made this using abilba seed,
sag leaves, and oolah fish bone.
Whoa, that tastes exactly like soy sauce!
You're right, I made the sauce
for the sandwich out of that.
Amazing, it's perfect.
Have you thought about selling
this because you'd make a fortune?
You think it's that good?
Wait, you can't sell it
But, why not?
Because there wouldn't be any left for me.
My god, you're so greedy.
If you like it that much,
I could always make more.
Hey, Kirito!
How you doing, buddy?
Hey, Klein.
Still alive, huh?
Jeez, you're the same as ever.
Wait.
Whoa, you're a solo player.
What the heck are you doing with a...
girl?
Uh, um, I could have sworn you guys
met before at one of the boss fights.
I'll introduce you.
This is Klein of the Foo-Rin Kazan Guild.
And this is Asuna of the
Knights of the Blood Oath.
Hey, come on, say something.
What's wrong?
You lagging?
Hi, I'm Klein.
I'm 24 and single and looking for...
Boss!
Whoa!
Are you really that awesome?
Don't worry, it's cool.
These guys are okay.
Yeah, but I don't know about Klein.
What the hell?
That's payback, you weasel.
Come on, Klein.
What are you doing with a girl?
Holding out on me.
What's the deal, man? Spill it.
Uh, well... Excuse me.
Kirito and I are together
because we're sort of in a party.
Huh?
Kirito, you son of a...
Wait, it's not what you think.
Kirito.
What the hell?
It's an army.
That's the big guild that runs floor one.
What are they doing up here?
They were almost slaughtered on floor 25.
Instead of clearing levels, they've
been trying to build up their numbers.
I haven't seen them on the
front lines in a while.
At ease!
I'm with the Aincrad Liberation
Army, Lieutenant Colonel Korvats.
I'm Kirito, Solo.
Sure you are.
Have you cleared the area up ahead?
Yeah.
We also got a map with
directions to the boss room.
Hmm.
Right.
Then hand over that map
and we'll be on our way.
You want us to just give it to you?
You even know how much of a
pain in the ass mapping is?
We share our information and resources
with civilian players all the time!
And we don't charge a thing for it!
We maintain order in the chaos of battle,
so that all players can leave
this world as quickly as possible!
Therefore, it's your duty
to cooperate with us!
So hand over that map!
Listen, you!
You bastard! Easy.
When we got back to town, I was going
to go public with the map anyway.
It's cool. Oh, now wait. Come on, man.
You're being way too nice to him.
I don't care about making
money off map data.
Thanks for cooperating.
By the way, if you're planning to hit
the boss, I wouldn't recommend it.
That is my decision to make.
Hey, I just took a look
inside that room, pal.
And you can't beat that boss
if your troops are half dead.
Look at them.
They're exhausted.
Nonsense.
My men are tougher than that.
They won't quit until I say so.
On your feet.
Come on, move.
Oh, man.
Are those guys going to be okay?
I'm sure they know what they're doing.
They won't rush the boss without
checking it out first, right?
Maybe we should keep an eye on him anyway.
I don't know who's nicer, you or me.
So, anyway, Asuna, I got a favor to ask.
He can be hard to talk to, and he's
a loner and addicted to combat,
but he's a good guy.
Take care of him, will ya?
Okay.
I promise, he's in good hands.
That's the last one.
Only thing left's the boss's room.
Maybe those guys used some kind of
teleportation thingy to go back.
Asuna!
Ray!
Idiots!
Hey!
You guys okay?
Don't just stand there!
Use your teleport crystals! We can't!
The crystals aren't working!
I've never heard of a trap like
this being in a boss room before.
The Uncrant Liberation Army
doesn't know the word retreat!
Come on!
Keep fighting! They're insane.
Hey, what the hell's going on?
They can't use their
teleportation crystals.
We could distract the boss, but
going in there is too risky.
But isn't there something we can do?
Ready?
CHARGE!
Don't do it!
Hey!
Hang on, Korvats.
I can't believe it.
No.
I can't.
Oh, what the hell?
Get out!
I got you, buddy.
Thanks.
This'll take forever.
Get out of there! Kirito!
The only way to end this is if I use it.
But then...
Damn it!
Just use it already!
Hey, Klein! Asuna! Listen!
I need ten seconds!
Keep him off me!
Yeah, you got it!
Okay, I'm ready!
Switch out!
Okay, here goes.
Starburst stream!
What the hell kind of skill is that?
Faster!
Gotta go faster!
Is it...
over?
Kirito!
Wake up, Kirito!
Oh, man, my head.
That was too close.
How long was I out for?
Just a few seconds.
You reckless!
Eddie!
Jeez, don't hug me so hard.
I'll lose the last of my HP.
Korvats and two of his men are
the only ones who didn't make it.
We haven't lost a player in
a boss fight since Floor 67.
That wasn't a boss fight.
That was suicide.
Korvats was a damn fool.
There's no point to
any of this if you die.
You're not off the hook either.
What the hell did you do just now?
I don't think you want to know.
Oh, come on!
I've never seen anything like that before!
It's an extra skill I picked up.
Dual wielding.
Dude, are there prerequisites?
If I knew that, I'd have shared it by now.
It's not on the Infobroker skill list.
Guess it's exclusive to you.
Hey, you got a unique skill.
Way to stay on the down low, Kirito.
How can you keep an awesome secret
like this from your buddies?
About six months ago, I was scrolling
through my skill menu, and it was just...
there.
Dual wielding.
But if anyone else found out
I had a skill like this...
They'd get pissed because you
had something they didn't.
Some gamers are like that, but not me.
You're right, though.
People would definitely
be jealous you had that.
And that.
Well, they say your character's
built by life's challenges,
so keep soldiering on, young man.
Easier said than done.
We're gonna go trigger the warp gate.
You coming?
Nah, I'll catch up with you later.
Need to rest for a bit.
I heard that.
Have a safe trip back.
Oh, and by the way... Huh?
You know how you ran in there?
To rescue those army guys like you did?
Yeah.
Well, you know, I'm glad you did.
Anyway, I'll see ya.
What's wrong, Asuna?
I was so scared.
If you died, I didn't know what I'd do.
What are you talking about?
You're the one who jumped
in first, remember?
I'm taking a leave of absence from the
guild. Why? And do what? Sleep in all day?
Did you forget already?
I said I was teaming up with you.
A blue demon that annihilated a
big squad of army guys and a 50
-hit combo from a dual wielder
who took out the boss by himself.
I can't believe what a big deal
they're making out of this thing.
Yeah, it's blowing up right in my face.
A buttload of swordsmen and info brokers
showed up at my place this morning.
Now I need a new pad because
they know where I live.
Yeah, well, that's sort
of kind of your own fault.
You said it was going
to be our little secret,
but you went and blabbed it to everyone.
What are we gonna do, Kirito?
We've got ourselves a huge
problem outside of boss fights.
I don't believe we've
ever actually met, Kirito.
Well, there was that
conference on floor 67.
We talked a little bit there.
Commander Heathcliff.
Yes, that was a difficult
battle, wasn't it?
We almost lost a few players there too.
We may be the top guild, but we barely
get by with the amount of troops we have.
And now here you are trying to
poach one of our best players.
I don't know what to say.
If she's that important, maybe you should
do a better job picking her bodyguard.
You have my sincerest apologies for any
trouble you might have had with Kuradeel.
But you must understand
that we simply cannot
allow our second in
command to leave the guild,
just like that.
If you want her, you'll have to use
your dual blades to take her from us.
If you can defeat me in combat,
you'll be free to take Asuna with you.
On the other hand, if you lose, you
will join the Knights of the Blood Oath.
Yeah, okay.
If you want to settle this
with swords, that's fine by me.
We'll have ourselves a duel then.
What did you hear?
The last one you saw on the morning...
I was very frozen to the night.
When I hear you, the
sound of a little cold.
It's a little late for you to
come to the light. I hear you.
My heart's at a little bit more,
I hear you.
My heart's at a time
Thank
you.
My world's true if we're in a dream.
Even if we're in trouble,
but in the deep end,
I'm always, always playing.
I'm slowly, slowly, shining.
Crimson killing intent.